<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>App Showcase</title>
    <description>Ever wondered who is building amazing apps using PhoneGap?</description>
    <link>http://phonegap.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://phonegap.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 05:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 05:00:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>snowbuddy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;During our second alpine company meeting, we were looking for ski apps to use on the mountain. After downloading and testing a few of the ‘top apps’, we discovered some major flaws and omissions. These apps only really tracked speed, distance and calories and although some apps give you other useful data such as resort information and weather there was a serious lack of design and fun. Constantly competing to beat yours and your friends’ top speeds is not only challenging (most people can only hit a certain top speed and can rarely exceed it, particularly on a weeks’ ski trip) but it is also dangerous. It’s not about pushing yourself to the point of losing control, it’s about riding the mountain in perfect control, and having fun while doing it. For us, being on the mountain with your mates was more about having fun. So that’s what we made snowbuddy all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We used PhoneGap for snowbuddy as we wanted to develop the application quickly and have it on both Android &amp;amp; iOS. As it was originally for internal use, speed of development was crucial to us as well as cross platform support. For this, we believe PhoneGap was the best solution for us to use. We are really happy with how the app has turned out, and especially how well it performs on iOS. We’ve even had some developers question whether we were using Swift or Objective-C for it… Well no, we are using PhoneGap, but we do have some custom native plugins that we’ve used, both open source and ones we have made ourselves. We decided that other people might also enjoy using snowbuddy, so we released it to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 17:04:40 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/snowbuddy</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/snowbuddy</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BrowserQuest</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;BrowserQuest is a small multiplayer game inviting you to explore a world of adventure from your Windows Phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You play as a young warrior driven by the thrill of adventure. No princess to save here, just a dangerous world filled with treasures to discover. As you discover more of the world, you can try to complete the built in quests/achievements or fight against other players.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what are you waiting for? Download the game right now and start your journey into the unknown and mysterious world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: This version of BrowserQuest is a extended version, which has been extended with a player level system and PvP fights, so the game feels a little bit longer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Support: If you experience any errors, then please contact us by e-mail (apps@mpbrun.dk), as we cannot contact you through a review. We can then fix possible errors very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.phonegapwpchallenge.com/&quot;&gt;Windows Phone App Porting Challenge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 15:17:07 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/browserquest</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/browserquest</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Heart Camera</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Let’s decorate your photos with lovely hearts!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cute Stickers of hearts - You can use many cute heart stickers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Filters like Instagram - You can use photo filter effects similar to Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Auto Decorating - Once you bring a device close to your heart for 3 seconds, your photo will be decorated automatically! It’s amazing, try it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Share - You can share your cute photos on Instagram, Tumblr, Facebook, Twitter, LINE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The culture of “Deco” (photo-decoration) is a big part of Japanese youth culture. With that in mind, we decided to create a photo editing app witha simple heart theme. We added an auto-decoration function that is amazing and heart warming to this app,” said Ryo Kawanobe, creator of My Heart Camera. “As we are web developers, we choose PhoneGap because we wanted the flexibility to release on both iOS and Android while also being able to easily access plugins.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 00:22:06 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/my-heart-camera</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/my-heart-camera</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yoga+Travel</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you ever leave home for business or leisure travel and miss your favorite yoga class? In a new city and don’t know where to take class or can’t fit class into your busy schedule? This is the app for you! Yoga+Travel is the ideal app to take your yoga practice with you on the road. With safe, fun and effective sequenced classes for all levels, you never have to leave home without taking your yoga with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.phonegapwpchallenge.com/&quot;&gt;Windows Phone App Porting Challenge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 14:32:47 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/yoga-travel</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/yoga-travel</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sworkit Pro</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Awesome Randomized Circuit Training Workouts that keep you motivated to exercise and stay fit. Choose the part of body to workout and for how long. Sworkit creates the perfect workout anywhere, anytime. No weights or extra equipment required.
4.5+ Stars. First time app developer. Listed in Apple’s in the Featured Health &amp;amp; Fitness, Get in Shape section.
Press: Lifehacker.com | Gizmodo.com | Greatist.com | Brit.co | Addictivetips.com
Plugins: LowLatency, Video, Google Anlaytics, Kiip Rewards..&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 11:56:02 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/sworkit-pro</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/sworkit-pro</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TripCase</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;TripCase is an intelligent, all-knowing mobile app that guides you through every stage of your trip, making you the smartest, smoothest traveler around. With TripCase, you’ll be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PREPARED&lt;/strong&gt;: Save time and end confusion with all your trip details located in one spot.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;CONNECTED&lt;/strong&gt;: Rest easy knowing you have the latest info or alerts about your trip (and that important contacts are kept in the loop, too).&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;BRILLIANT&lt;/strong&gt;: Travel smarter and experience more thanks to relevant and timely messages and alerts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 09:28:13 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/tripcase</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/tripcase</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>HealthTap</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;HealthTap is the best way to quickly find, trusted, reputable doctor answers to health questions anytime, anywhere for free!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✓ Get fast, free, trustworthy health answers
on any symptom, condition, medication or health concern from over 14,000 of the best U.S. doctors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✓ Connect with doctors
by starting private conversations in a safe, HIPAA-secure environment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✓ Share securely with doctors
Privately share scans, images and other health related documents with doctors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✓ and more, for FREE!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 20:29:39 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/healthtap-find-doctors-and-free-answers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/healthtap-find-doctors-and-free-answers</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Untappd</title>
        <description>Untappd is a mobile app that allows you to socially share the brew you&#39;re currently enjoying, as well as where you&#39;re enjoying it, with your friends! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Our mobile and web applications allow users to share, discovery and engage each other within the world of beer. Known as &quot;the Foursquare for beer,” user can check-in to what they’re drinking and where and share with their friends on Untappd, Twitter, Facebook, &amp;amp; Foursquare.&lt;br /&gt;

FEATURES

- Easily discover new beers and bars near your location
- See where you’re friends are drinking and meet up with them
- Personalized beer recommendations based on the tastes of you and your friends
- Find where you can get a specific beer nearby
- Share ratings, reviews and photos of your favorite beers with your friends
- Post your activity and photos to your Twitter, Facebook and Foursquare
- Create a wish list of beers you want to try in the future
- Unlock a variety of badges for trying different styles and places
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 22:30:26 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/untappd/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/untappd/</guid>
        
        
        <category>app</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hockey Community</title>
        <description>Hockey Community&#39;s goal is to make hockey more social and accessible around the world. We help anyone in the hockey industry connecting with players, rinks, games and more! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
- Create a page for all of the teams you belong to and connect with all its members in one place.&lt;br /&gt;
- Arrive at your rink and get the option to Check-In with the team you are playing with.&lt;br /&gt;
- Discover the rinks around you and CHECK-IN. HC will then keep track of how many times you&#39;ve played hockey around the world!
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;New!&lt;/b&gt; As of November 2012, the latest version of Hockey Community allows players to track how often they play, share events, check-ins or photos, and see what other people are doing with a newsfeed.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;PhoneGap has pushed us to learn and embrace HTML5 at its best, &quot; said Amrit Kahlon, Software Engineer. &quot;Today we&#39;re able to work on one source code for one iPhone app, one iPad app, our mobile site and soon an Android app.
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 22:55:38 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/hockey-community/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/hockey-community/</guid>
        
        
        <category>app</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bit Timer</title>
        <description>This app is designed for the no-frills, hard-core workout.  This is the first interval timer you’ll see with a set up that is this fast and easy.  Your workout should be intense, not your workout set up. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
1. Super Simple Set up. &lt;br /&gt;
Get to your workout in no time with a clean, simple, no-frills design.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

2. Distinct tones that guide you through your workout. &lt;br /&gt;
We chose clear, easy-to-distinguish tones for each portion of your workout.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

3. Work out to music with out missing a beat. &lt;br /&gt;
Music automatically fades, allowing you to hear interval tones.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Features:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
- Press and Drag to set Work, Rest, and Repeat.&lt;br /&gt;
- Work Periods: 5s to 2min. Rest Periods: 0s (no rest) to 2min. Up to 40 repeats.&lt;br /&gt;
- 10 second count down allows you to get into place before your workout starts.&lt;br /&gt;
- Three distinct sounds to designate where you are in your workout.&lt;br /&gt;
- Countdown tone gives warning before Work starts.&lt;br /&gt;
- Pause your workout at any time and restart right where you left off.&lt;br /&gt;
- Music automatically fades, allowing you to hear interval tones.&lt;br /&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 23:42:19 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://phonegap.github.io/app/bit-timer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://phonegap.github.io/app/bit-timer/</guid>
        
        
        <category>app</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
